

PROGRAMMER ANALYST

□ (+1) 310-941-3409 | kmng73@gmail.com | □ kmng | □ stefantopia | ¥ @stefantopia

Professional Summary

Web Application Developer with proven ability to design and implement solutions in health care industry, bring strong expertises and experiences in various application platforms, design patterns and development paradigms. Strong commitments in following industry best practices, maintaining communication with customers and establish long-term maintainability of the products, known for ability to develop expectional application from beginning to the end.

Skills

Programming Java, Groovy, PHP, Javascript, TypeScript, Python, C, C++, C#, VB.NET, SQL, HTML, CSS, Bash, ETFX

Web Grails, Laravel, Angular, React, ¡Query

Databases MySQL, Access, SQLite, MS SQL server ,MongoDB **Servers** Linux, Window Server, AWS, Docker, Puppet

Management Project Management

Work Experience

Department of Radiological Sciences, UCLA

Los Angeles, CA USA

PROGRAMMER/ANALYST IV

Aug 2018 - Present

- Work as system architect and technical lead for two large scale projects
- Design and Develop next generation of Faculty academic productivity metrics application using latest services based architecture to improve agility and performance. The application is implemented using RESTful API backend with Java/Grail environment and Spring Framework and Single Page Application Frontend with JavaScript/Typescript environment and Angular 7 framework
- · Develop implementation and release plan to enable rapid development cycle and improve adoptation to requirements changes
- · Work with system operation team using Puppet to provision both development and production environment to ensure stability of the application
- Provide mentorship and work assignment to a Programmer/Analyst III
- Provide program management experties and set up team project management environment using GitLab platform to promote collaboration and improve team communication

Department of Radiological Sciences, UCLA

Los Angeles, CA USA

PROGRAMMER/ANALYST III

Dec 2015 - Aug 2018

- Design and Develop Web-based Application to generate academic performance metrics of faculty academic productivity by integrating multiple internal and external data sources, serve more than 100 faculties, administrative assistants, fund managers, clinical trials study coordinators and department executive for academic personnel decision. The application was showcased multiple times in UC-wide conferences. The application is developed using Java/Grails environment with Spring Framework
- Design and Develop Web-based Application to handle clinical trials requests from the whole institution to the department. The application is known as the golden standard for clinical trial management system. The application is developed using PHP/MySql environment with Laravel Framework

School of Engineering Distance Learning Network, USC

Los Angeles, CA USA

PROGRAMMER/ANALYST III

Dec 2012 - Dec 2015

- · Collaborate with a team of developers to design and develop online learning environment and supporting tools using PHP with Oracle backend
- Design and Develop internal administration tools to support students, faculty and administrators in the remote learning environment

Dept of Medicine, UCLA Medical Center

Los Angeles, CA USA

SR. INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SPECIALIST

Sep 2009 - Dec 2012

- Design and Develop patient medical records and data collection system for the Dept. of Medicine (DOM) outpatient program, as well as the hospital's internal medicine and urgent care facilities
- Manage all web-based systems for DOM Education Office to meet various departmental needs
- Design and develop a web-based, HIPPA compliant physician note system that readily permits exchange of information between primary physicians, consultants and other care providers, as well as rapid recoding of necessary data for record-keeping
- Support, maintain and expand existing medical reminder system to tract therapies, needed diagnostic studies, follow-ups, appointment, etc for monitoring of patient's care processes
- · Create and develop a secure online patient-physician email based corresponding and prescription system
- · Perform ongoing project development and site maintenance functions for various DOM websites

Los Angeles, CA USA

Programmer/Analyst II

Jun 2003 - Sep 2009

- Designed, Developed and Maintained Web solution for the Department of Medicine
- Developed Enterprise Patient Record and Preventive Screening Reminder (Expert) System (Outpatient Signout) with connection to MCCS web services
- Designed and maintained Website for Department of Medicine (Housestaff and Schedules)
- Constructed and Designed the Website portal for Dept. of Medicine
- · Constructed multi-hosts testing environment using SME server (customized Red Hat 7.3 Linux server)
- · Developed and maintained various websites in the Department of Medicine including Office of Research Administration Website

Education

UCLA Extension, Los Angeles

Los Angeles, CA USA

PROJECT MANAGEMENT CERTIFICATION

2004

2001

University of Califonia, Los Angeles

Los Angeles, CA USA

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

• GPA 3.8

University of Califonia, Los Angeles

Los Angeles, CA USA

M.S. IN PHYSICS

• GPA 3.8

Chinese University of Hong Kong

Hong Kong, Hong Kong

M.S. IN PHYSICS
• GPA 3.8

Chinese University of Hong Kong

Hong Kong, Hong Kong

B.S. IN PHYSICS
• GPA 3.7

Professional Development

Profesional Development Program

Los Angeles, CA USA

UCLA

2019